{
    "subject": "resource/Ella_Fitzgerald's_Christmas",
    "predicate": "property/recorded",
    "object": "--07-17",
    "human_readable": "Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas was recorded on July 17.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8998602628707886,
            "question": "When was Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas recorded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8249263763427734,
            "question": "On what date was Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas album recorded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8137234449386597,
            "question": "Where was Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas recorded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6592112183570862,
            "question": "What month was Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas recording completed in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.605858325958252,
            "question": "Were there any notable guest performers on Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas recording?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5873658657073975,
            "question": "Is there information about the specific songs included in Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas recording?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5774086713790894,
            "question": "Who produced Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas album?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.505463719367981,
            "question": "Does the title 'Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas' refer to a specific album?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4458565413951874,
            "question": "How popular was Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas album upon its release?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37177804112434387,
            "question": "What type of music is likely featured in 'Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas was recorded on July 17.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2185_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How popular was Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas album upon its release?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2185_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does the title 'Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas' refer to a specific album?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2185_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who produced Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas album?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2185_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2185_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2185_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2185_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2185_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2185_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2185_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2185_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2185_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2185_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2185_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents indicate that \"Ella Fitzgerald's Christmas\" was recorded on July 17 and 18, 1967. This information supports the query that the album was recorded on July 17 (and likely also on July 18), hence the answer is \"yes\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}